atlanticwavemusic.com 2011-03-07

# Privacy Policy | Atlantic Wave Radio

We have developed this policy so that you can feel confident about the privacy and security of the personal information that you provide to us.

**Disclosure of information**

Atlantic Wave Radio complies with and is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 in the United Kingdom. We take all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to and use of your personal data.

Our volunteers maintain a responsibility to keep your information confidential and will only use it to offer relevant information related to your enquiry.

Any personal details that we use to provide or promote ourselves to you (e.g. name, address, email address, telephone number) will not be passed to any third party organisation for marketing purposes without your permission and will not be used by us for any purpose other than that which you requested.

The Internet is not a secure medium. However to protect your data we put in place various security procedures including use of firewalls, backup measures, we limit access to data to relevant personnel and password protect all machinery holding personal data.

**Cookies**

Atlantic Wave Radio’s web site uses “cookies”. A ‘cookie’ is a piece of information that is held on your PC, which enables our website to recognise you on subsequent visits and allows us to tailor your visit to your specific requirements.

**Email**

Atlantic Wave Radio complies with the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 in the United Kingdom.

We respect the privacy of personal email accounts and we store your email address as securely as any other personal information we hold. We will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail and your details will not be passed to any organisation outside Atlantic Wave Radio without your explicit permission.

If you have given us permission, we may use email to send you messages to keep you up to date with news about ourselves, as well as anything you express an interest in, either online or through other contact with us

**Comments/Forum**

If you voluntarily disclose personal information on the forum or in comment areas on this website, that information can also be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. We are not responsible for the content posted by users of these services. Use or exchange of profane or sexually explicit comments or material on the website comment areas or forum is prohibited. In particular, users must not make sexually explicit or suggestive comments to minors. The posting of any unlawful material is also prohibited.

**Third party sites**

Third party internet sites that you can link through to from our website are not covered by our Privacy and Security policy, so we accept no responsibility or liability for these sites.
